Eternity has a price.
The Old Guard 2 is a action, fantasy film directed by Victoria Mahoney.
Andy and her team of immortal warriors fight with renewed purpose as they face a
powerful new foe threatening their mission to protect humanity.
Andromache of Scythia / Andy, played by Charlize Theron.
Nile Freeman, played by KiKi Layne.
Sebastien Le Livre / Booker, played by Matthias Schoenaerts.
Yusuf Al-Kaysani / Joe, played by Marwan Kenzari.
Nicolò di Genova / Nicky, played by Luca Marinelli.
Quynh, played by Veronica Ngo.
The Old Guard 2 is a 2025 American superhero film directed by Victoria
Mahoney, from a screenplay by Greg Rucka and Sarah L.
Walker, based on the comic book The Old Guard by Rucka and Leandro Fernández.
Serving as a sequel to the first film, the film stars Charlize Theron, KiKi Layne, Matthias Schoenaerts, Marwan Kenzari, Luca Marinelli,
Veronica Ngô, and Chiwetel Ejiofor reprising their roles from the first film while Henry Golding and Uma Thurman join the cast.
The Old Guard 2 was released on July 2, 2025, on Netflix and received generally
mixed-to-negative reviews from critics, calling it inferior to its predecessor.
The film was the final film to be produced by Skydance
before its merger with Paramount Global.
The film explores themes of immortality, based on comic,
interracial romance, lgbt, found family.